andomedia.com 2016-03-20

# Triton Digital - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which Triton Digital Inc.( **“Triton Digital”** , **“we”** , **“us”** , **“our”** ) collects, uses, discloses and otherwise manages personal information of visitors of tritondigital.com (the "Site"). This policy does not apply to the use of products and services provided by us on behalf of our clients. To read the privacy policy that applies to our streaming, advertising, engagement, contests and/or sweepstakes (collectively the “ **Services** ”), [click here](http://tritondigital.com/privacy-policy-services).

Please note that our privacy policy has changed. To access the most current version of our [privacy policy](http://tritondigital.com/privacy-policy-services), click here. This policy also does not apply to the audience management services. Please read it carefully. We also invite you to review our Terms of Use.  
Because we are committed to respect the privacy of our users and because the success of the Site is dependent on building and maintaining goodwill with our users, we are committed to implementing measures designed to respect and protect your privacy. Moreover, we see it as our responsibility to set an example, and to help establish standards for privacy on the Internet.

Triton reviews its privacy practices from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. To contact us about privacy issues, to report a violation of our Privacy Policy, or to raise any other issue, please e-mail us at: [privacy@tritondigital.com](mailto:privacy@tritondigital.com.).

## The Personal Information We Collect

You may visit our Site without providing any of your personal information to us. At this time, the only personal information that we collect through our Site is personal information that you voluntarily provide to us through the "Contact" portion of the Site. The information collected through the "Contact" portion of the Site consists in the name, e-mail address, and any comment you wish to add.

We may also automatically collect general anonymous information related to your use of our Site, such as the date and time you visit the Site and the pages you visit on the Site. Our servers may also automatically collect information about the type of browser you use and the name of your Internet Service Provider. In addition, we may collect "cookie" information from your browser to identify your computer and provide us with a record of your visits to our Site (Collectively, the foregoing is referred to as "Usage Data"). The technology is used to gather "cookie" information that is provided by the Internet browser you use, and is stored on your computer.

## How We Use (and Do Not Use) the Personal Information

Any personal information you provide to us when you send us an email is used solely to identify who you are and to respond to the purpose for which you submitted the message. We use Usage Data for the purposes of monitoring and improving the use and features of the Website.

## Third-Party Links

The Site contains links to other Internet web sites, which may include co-branded or other affiliated sites. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies which we recommend you read carefully. We have no control over such sites and therefore have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations who operate such linked sites may collect, use, disclose or otherwise treat your personal information.

Nevertheless, in the event you encounter any third party associated with the Site (or who claims association with the Site) who you feel is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact [privacy@tritondigital.com](mailto:privacy@tritondigital.com.) and we will be happy to forward your message to the third party.

## Security of Personal Information

We will maintain your personal information in secure data storage to safeguard it from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We will maintain the strict confidentiality of all personal information collected, and will only disclose such information on a confidential basis to employees and third-party contractors of Triton Digital who require such information for the purposes set out above. We will only keep your personal information for as long as it remains necessary or relevant for the purposes stated above or as otherwise required by law.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, you should be aware that, unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, Triton Digital does not represent, warrant or guarantee that personal information will be protected against loss, misuse or alteration and does not accept any liability for personal information submitted by you, nor for your or third parties’ use or misuse of personal information.

## Changing or deleting personal information

If you would like to have your personally identifiable information removed from the Site's database, please contact us at [privacy@tritondigital.com ](mailto:privacy@tritondigital.com.)and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within the Site's databases, access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however, we reserve the right, from time to time, to re-contact former TritonDigital.com users.

## Questions?

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to [legal@tritondigital.com](mailto:legal@tritondigital.com).

Updated April 24, 2014
